<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cyanogen on Khalid Scratch Board</title>
    <link>http://khal.web.id/tags/cyanogen/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cyanogen on Khalid Scratch Board</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://khal.web.id/tags/cyanogen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Cyanogen nightly Auto Update</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2015/04/14/diy-cyanogen-nightly-auto-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2015/04/14/diy-cyanogen-nightly-auto-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://khal.web.id/images/wpid-wp-1428958109831.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://khal.web.id/images/wpid-wp-1428958109831.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;wp-1428958109831&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Instead of waiting and whining when will your OnePlus One get an OTA update, you could just quickly fetch the latest nightly build from CyanogenMod.org download page, &lt;strong&gt;just be careful not to download ROM that&amp;rsquo;s not suitable with your phone or else it will bricked your phone&lt;/strong&gt;, as an example if your phone is OnePlus One, Bacon is the only ROM that you need to download.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before going further, your phone need to be rooted and have one of these two recovery software installed, either ClockworkMod or TWRP recovery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[spoiler title=&amp;ldquo;How to Root and Unlock your device&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You need &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.androidcentral.com/installing-android-sdk-windows-mac-and-linux-tutorial&#34;&gt;Fastboot and ADB&lt;/a&gt; installed on you PC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1. After Fastboot and ADB installed, go to your terminal windows, and do this next step

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;./fastboot oem unlock (You can skip this step if your phone’s bootloader is already unlocked).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;./fastboot flash recovery . Image file should be the TWRP recovery image.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;./fastboot reboot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[/spoiler]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After one of the recovery above installed, make sure that you create a Nandroid backup from the recovery system and copy that backup to your external drive or PC.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to download the Gapps if you still want to use Google Play and friends. You may download the latest signed zip on &lt;a href=&#34;http://wiki.cyanogenmod.org/w/Google_Apps&#34;&gt;CyanogenMod.org&lt;/a&gt; websites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CM version of Gapps that you&amp;rsquo;re about to download must be the same with the ROM version that you&amp;rsquo;re going to flash/install, or else you might having a bootloop when rebooting your phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OK then here comes the magic where CyanDelta lets you update your CyanogenMod ROM by downloading just a small file (about 10 MB) instead of a big full zip file (about 200 MB) each time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may &lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.cyandelta&amp;amp;feature=nav_result#?t=W251bGwsMSwxLDMsImNvbS5jeWFuZGVsdGEiXQ..&#34;&gt;install CyanDelta updater&lt;/a&gt; from playstore or check their website at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cyandelta.com&#34;&gt;www.cyandelta.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that you have 2 downloaded files, the CM12 ROM zipped and CM12 Gapps signed zipped. Copy these files to your phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open the CyanDelta updater and then import your ROM file to CyanDelta,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://khal.web.id/images/wpid-wp-1428957353905.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://khal.web.id/images/wpid-wp-1428957353905.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; title=&#34;wp-1428957353905&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there is an available update, please do update the file first before installing the ROM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the installation takes longer than it should, turn off your phone, reboot into recovery mode, wipe data/factory reset, and then reboot system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all installation step is finished, you may reboot once again into recovery mode and then install the Gapps signed zip file, reboot system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy your nightly ROM, don&amp;rsquo;t forget to install CyanUpdater once again after a factory reset.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>