<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>smartwatch on Khalid&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://khal.web.id/tags/smartwatch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in smartwatch on Khalid&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 23:08:09 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://khal.web.id/tags/smartwatch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Shades of Smartwatch</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2018/08/06/20-Shades-of-Smartwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 23:08:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2018/08/06/20-Shades-of-Smartwatch/</guid>
      <description>Had enough with all smartwatch vendor these days, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to give my feedback base on 3 years experience using the pebble watch.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to share about what feature is really working or not, and if you are a smartwatch maker that just happens reading this blog I&amp;rsquo;m hoping this post will be a clue for your next flagship idea.
It&amp;rsquo;s all more to smartwatch functionality, I don&amp;rsquo;t care whether it comes with a fancy strap, stainless/plastic body, or a screen made by a gorilla, as long as it is sturdy enough, it&amp;rsquo;s ok with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ahh.. a Dreadful battery life, Is it a Smartwatch, a Cellphone or just another complicated gadget?</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2014/08/18/ahh-a-dreadful-battery-life-is-it-a-smartwatch-a-cellphone-or-just-another-complicated-gadget/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 13:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2014/08/18/ahh-a-dreadful-battery-life-is-it-a-smartwatch-a-cellphone-or-just-another-complicated-gadget/</guid>
      <description>Big vendors of wearable hardware are keep pushing themself to put their grip in the race of smartwatch technology, they seem to compete with who can have a fancy and killer feature. Some feature such as call from watch, texting, voice recognition, listen to music, expensive glass, heart rate sensor, overkill notification, fancy screen color, builtin camera, builtin gps, and etc. But still, you need to pair the watch with your daily phone to get it work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>