<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>macos on Khalid&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://khal.web.id/tags/macos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in macos on Khalid&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>contact@khal.web.id (Khalid Adisendjaja)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>contact@khal.web.id (Khalid Adisendjaja)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:40:18 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://khal.web.id/tags/macos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rusty Macbook Air getting new Air from Archlinux</title>
      <link>https://khal.web.id/2018/01/25/Rusty-Macbook-Air-getting-new-Air-from-Archlinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:40:18 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>contact@khal.web.id (Khalid Adisendjaja)</author>
      <guid>https://khal.web.id/2018/01/25/Rusty-Macbook-Air-getting-new-Air-from-Archlinux/</guid>
      <description>Today I accidentally deleted my primary OSX partition from my very old MacBook air 4,2 (2011) with the last installed os was el Capitan. From the beginning, I just want to give my MacBook some extra space but it turns out cleaning all the HDD &amp;hellip;LOL, I seriously don&amp;rsquo;t know how in the hell this could happen, this is a lesson for not to clean your HDD in the middle of the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nge-mix Android di Macbook/PC</title>
      <link>https://khal.web.id/2016/01/25/nge-mix-android-di-macbookpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 13:02:42 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>contact@khal.web.id (Khalid Adisendjaja)</author>
      <guid>https://khal.web.id/2016/01/25/nge-mix-android-di-macbookpc/</guid>
      <description>Mungkin banyak yg sudah pada tahu kelebihan Android ini, tetapi kebanyakan orang terbiasa tahu bahwa android hanya running di henpon, tablet, IOT devices, atau mini PC dengan USB stick.
Meskipun bisa di install di banyak device, akan tetapi Operating System yang terinstall pun adalah notabene sama seperti yg kita lihat pada android phone/tablet kebanyakan, misal meski bernama android mini PC, OS yg terinstall pun adalah varian untuk tablet device.
Berawal dari sebuah company bernama JIDE Technology yg diusung oleh 3 ex-Google membuat sebuah OS bernama Remix OS berdasarkan project open source Android-X86.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>