<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>facebook on Khalid&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://khal.web.id/tags/facebook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in facebook on Khalid&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 07:25:20 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://khal.web.id/tags/facebook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Uhuk.. facebook &#34;ask&#34; buat gombalin cewek jomblo, lumayan neh</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2014/06/05/uhuk-facebook-ask-buat-gombalin-cewek-jomblo-lumayan-neh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 07:25:20 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2014/06/05/uhuk-facebook-ask-buat-gombalin-cewek-jomblo-lumayan-neh/</guid>
      <description>Kalo misal lo liat facebook profile temen lo yang lagi ga punya status relationship lo bakal bisa ngelihat tombol &amp;ldquo;Ask&amp;rdquo; button, yang dimana lo bisa tanya apapun itu yang berhubungan dengan status relationship orang tersebut, button &amp;ldquo;Ask&amp;rdquo; ini hanya bisa dilihat oleh orang lain, pemilik facebook profile tidak akan bisa melihat button ini.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mau punya Restoran di Facebook? Cekidot Gan!</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2014/05/26/mau-punya-restoran-di-facebook-cekidot-gan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 05:02:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2014/05/26/mau-punya-restoran-di-facebook-cekidot-gan/</guid>
      <description>Kabar gembira buat lo semua yang baru aja memulai bisnis resto/cafe/rumah makan/warteg atau yang sejenisnya.
Facebook baru2x aja merilis fitur baru dari Facebook Fan Pages dimana setiap user yang mempunyai facebook fan pages berkategorikan “Restaurant/Cafe” akan mempunyai opsi2x untuk menambahkan detil-detil tentang restoran yang dikelola oleh user tersebut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bicara soal &#34;People talking about this&#34;-nya Facebook fan page</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2013/12/12/bicara-soal-people-talking-about-this-nya-facebook-fan-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 09:50:44 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2013/12/12/bicara-soal-people-talking-about-this-nya-facebook-fan-page/</guid>
      <description>Wow topik lama nih, sumpah deh ga boong, kira-kira bulan Oktober tahun 2011 lalu, Facebook meluncurkan metrik baru buat Fan page insights yang namanya People talking about this ato biasa disingkat &amp;ldquo;PTAT&amp;rdquo; artinya berapa banyak orang yang ngomongin soal fan page lo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mari berbagi soal Privasi di Sosial Media Online</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2013/11/07/mari-berbagi-soal-privasi-di-sosial-media-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 07:21:35 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2013/11/07/mari-berbagi-soal-privasi-di-sosial-media-online/</guid>
      <description>Sebelum kita ngomongin soal privasi di sosial media online, tentunya kita harus tau dulu bentukan dari sosial media itu atau &amp;ldquo;Apa sih sosial media itu?&amp;rdquo;, sebenernya mudah saja untuk semua orang mendefinisikan artian dari sosial media (*baca: SosMed), tapi pada intinya SosMed adalah sebuah wadah dimana semua member/pengguna/partisipan bisa membangun relasi dan koneksi dengan member lain, tempat dimana kita bisa selalu terhubung dengan teman2x, menjalin hubungan baru, berbagi interest dan ide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Facebook Test User</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2011/07/27/using-facebook-test-user/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 08:59:35 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2011/07/27/using-facebook-test-user/</guid>
      <description>If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what Facebook Test User is? you may check the documentation on http://developers.facebook.com/docs/test_users/
Test User is a tool that could be handy when you need to have some users to interact with your application, facebook currently provide this through Graph Api.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook PHP SDK v3.01 now free cookies</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2011/07/06/facebook-php-sdk-v3-01-now-free-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 13:38:44 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2011/07/06/facebook-php-sdk-v3-01-now-free-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Now the new SDK has been released, on the beginning of june 2011 I guess.
Well the main different from v3.00 is? Now the CSRF state is rely on persistent data which is a session named &amp;ldquo;state&amp;rdquo; and not using cookie anymore!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profil Facebook lo jadi lapak ? Migrasi deh ke fan page!</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2011/06/24/profil-facebook-lo-jadi-lapak-migrasi-deh-ke-fan-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2011 10:00:12 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2011/06/24/profil-facebook-lo-jadi-lapak-migrasi-deh-ke-fan-page/</guid>
      <description>Belakangan ini banyak banget yang akun facebook pribadinya dijadiin lapak buat jualan, kadang jadi suka bikin bingung temennya sendiri, karena biasanya namanya jadi bukan namanya sendiri. Nah, sekarang Facebook punya solusi yaitu Facebook Fan Page, yang bisa dipakai buat lapak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting People Likes and Comments from facebook comment post </title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2011/03/15/getting-people-likes-and-comments-from-facebook-comment-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 07:19:33 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2011/03/15/getting-people-likes-and-comments-from-facebook-comment-post/</guid>
      <description>A simple way to know people likes and comment on your post or other people post is through Comment Graph Api, you will need an access token to use it, this might be useful when you want to count the total of people who likesyour post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook add access permission to Application Security</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2011/03/07/facebook-add-access-permission-to-application-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 08:45:37 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2011/03/07/facebook-add-access-permission-to-application-security/</guid>
      <description>Sometime when you made some apps, there were another user who wants to check about the insight of the app, or maybe just want to test the apps, back then you might have to give all access to a user through www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set a facebook session app from access token</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2011/03/03/set-a-facebook-session-for-you-apps-from-access-token/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 08:52:36 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2011/03/03/set-a-facebook-session-for-you-apps-from-access-token/</guid>
      <description>In some situation you will want to create a facebook session for your app, for example you get the code query string after user granted your app, now you can construct the url like below,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replacement of fb visible-to-connection for iframe apps on facebook page tabs</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2011/03/03/replacement-of-fb-visible-to-connection-for-iframe-apps-on-facebook-page-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 08:31:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2011/03/03/replacement-of-fb-visible-to-connection-for-iframe-apps-on-facebook-page-tabs/</guid>
      <description>Developing an Iframe app an somehow you want to use this FBML tag below.
&amp;lt;fb:visible-to-connection&amp;gt; Only connections should view this.. &amp;lt;/fb:visible-to-connection&amp;gt;  On each call from page tab you can get a signed_request variable, the value is like this below,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two ways to Login or Authenticate using Facebook JS SDK Dialog box</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2011/03/03/two-ways-to-login-or-authenticate-using-facebook-js-sdk-dialog-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 08:09:05 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2011/03/03/two-ways-to-login-or-authenticate-using-facebook-js-sdk-dialog-box/</guid>
      <description>There is two easy way to authenticate a user with Facebook JS SDK,
Using FB.UI,
FB.ui( { method: &#39;oauth&#39;, display:&#39;iframe&#39;, perms:APP_EXT_PERMISSIONS }, function(response) { if(response.session) { console.dir(response); if(redirectURL) location.href = redirectURL; } } );  Using FB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Ready for IFRAME Facebook App based</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2010/10/28/getting-ready-for-iframe-facebook-app-based/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 06:58:22 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2010/10/28/getting-ready-for-iframe-facebook-app-based/</guid>
      <description>At this time you need to be ready to migrate your facebook apps to Iframe based apps, because as it written on Facebook Developer Roadmap
 &amp;ldquo;We will stop allowing new FBML applications, but will continue to support existing FBML tabs and applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iframe on Facebook Fan Pages Tabs</title>
      <link>http://khal.web.id/2010/07/20/iframe-on-facebook-fan-pages-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 09:47:33 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khal.web.id/2010/07/20/iframe-on-facebook-fan-pages-tabs/</guid>
      <description>Iframe will not be supported on facebook fan pages tab, the strange thing is, it only happened on first load and the you&amp;rsquo;ll get this error iframe not supported
I just figured out that apps on Fan Pages Tab need an action from user, so then to get an iframe working on tab,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>