<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>coronavirus on Khalid&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://khal.web.id/tags/coronavirus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in coronavirus on Khalid&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>contact@khal.web.id (Khalid Adisendjaja)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>contact@khal.web.id (Khalid Adisendjaja)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 09:30:48 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://khal.web.id/tags/coronavirus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quite useful QR scans overcome Coronavirus in The World</title>
      <link>https://khal.web.id/2020/10/02/quite-useful-qr-scans-overcome-coronavirus-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 09:30:48 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>contact@khal.web.id (Khalid Adisendjaja)</author>
      <guid>https://khal.web.id/2020/10/02/quite-useful-qr-scans-overcome-coronavirus-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>In these past months, the auto-generated quick response codes, usually shortened as QR codes, have been used in so many countries over the world as a practical way to monitor the spread of coronavirus.
Each government of respective countries has been driving its system and campaign to introduce the usage of QR code to minimize the spread of coronavirus. The system has become mandatory for people and businesses to follow and doesn’t rule out the possibility of fines for not complying with the regulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji in Actions during this 2020 Awkwardness</title>
      <link>https://khal.web.id/2020/09/24/emoji-in-actions-during-this-2020-awkwardness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 04:58:35 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>contact@khal.web.id (Khalid Adisendjaja)</author>
      <guid>https://khal.web.id/2020/09/24/emoji-in-actions-during-this-2020-awkwardness/</guid>
      <description>These days, a lot of conversations happen and people have many ways to express their feeling whether it&amp;rsquo;s sad, angry, happy, or even desperation. Emoji is one thing that you could never miss its sighting. In fact, the way that people use emojis could be related to our current circumstances.
At this time being, it can’t be denied this is the year of the health-related emoji. The virus is everywhere 🦠, people wearing the mask 😷 all the time, which is an irony while France made mask compulsory in public but keep the ban on burqas and niqabs, people also got sick 🤢 sneezing 🤧 everywhere, unpredicted fever 🤒 tragically end up in a hospital 🤕 🚑 💊 💉 , and people always remind each other to wash your hands with 🧼 🧽</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indonesia&#39;s Skyrocketing Corona Outbreak</title>
      <link>https://khal.web.id/2020/09/14/indonesia-skyrocketing-corona-outbreak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 09:29:37 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>contact@khal.web.id (Khalid Adisendjaja)</author>
      <guid>https://khal.web.id/2020/09/14/indonesia-skyrocketing-corona-outbreak/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been 7 months since the #CoronaVirus encountered Indonesia, I remembered the news about a mother and her daughter were a suspect of #Covid19 infection from a Japanese foreigner, and till then, the outbreak is skyrocketing as no one cares.
Lack of testing and hasty actions to reopen public activities on a wide scale have kept Indonesia experiencing a spike in #Covid19 cases, the highest in Southeast Asia and past China.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>